(Leonard:)Well, that's it.
(Leonard:)That's the end of Roger Abbott.
(Raj:)And we still don't know
who framed him.
(Leonard:)I still keep thinking
(Leonard:)about how an entire life can
seemingly amount to nothing.
(Howard:)I guess the
sad truth is,
(Howard:)not everyone will
accomplish something great.
(Howard:)Some of us
(Howard:)may just have to find meaning
(Howard:)in the little moments
that make up life.
(Leonard:)That's a nice way
of looking at it.
(Howard:)Yeah for you, not for me.
(Howard:)I went to space. I'm covered.
(Leonard:)You know what?
(Leonard:)This bottle was meant
to celebrate an achievement.
(Leonard:)Let's make a pact.
(Leonard:)When one of us gets their
first big breakthrough,
(Leonard:)we'll celebrate by opening
this bottle of champagne
(Leonard:)and toasting
Professor Abbott.
(Howard:)I love that.
(Raj:)Yeah, me, too.
(Leonard:)Then, of course,